Repeat once for each backend.

Create 3 different users (User1, User2, User3).
Login with user 1.
Create 10 new polls using Q1 - Q10 from the data set below.
Logout.
Log in with user 2.
Create 5 new polls using Q11 - Q15 from the data set below.
Participate with 1 answer in polls Q1-Q10.
Add a comment to all polls Q1-Q10.
Log out.
Log in with user 3.
Create 10 new polls using Q16-Q25 from the data set below.
Enter at least 3 responses for each poll

{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Q1 - Who is the best Star Wars character?",
      "answers": ["Han Solo", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Luke Skywalker", "Princess Leia", "Darth Vader"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q2 -What is the most iconic scene in the original trilogy?",
      "answers": ["Darth Vader's reveal", "Death Star trench run", "Battle of Hoth", "Luke training with Yoda", "The rescue of Han Solo"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q3 - Which is the best movie of the original trilogy?",
      "answers": ["A New Hope", "The Empire Strikes Back", "Return of the Jedi"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q4 - Which creature or alien species is the most interesting?",
      "answers": ["Wookiees", "Ewoks", "Jawas", "Yoda's species", "Tusken Raiders"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q5 - What is the best vehicle or starship?",
      "answers": ["Millennium Falcon", "X-Wing", "TIE Fighter", "AT-AT Walker", "Slave I"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q6 - Who had the best lightsaber duel?",
      "answers": ["Luke vs. Vader (Empire Strikes Back)", "Luke vs. Vader (Return of the Jedi)", "Obi-Wan vs. Vader (A New Hope)"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q7 - What was the best moment for Han Solo?",
      "answers": ["Shooting Greedo", "Saving Luke on Hoth", "Rescuing Leia from the Death Star", "Flying into the asteroid field", "Freeing himself from carbonite"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q8 - Which secondary character would you want to know more about?",
      "answers": ["Boba Fett", "Lando Calrissian", "Admiral Ackbar", "Biggs Darklighter", "Wedge Antilles"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q9 - What is the best line from the original trilogy?",
      "answers": ["\"I am your father.\"", "\"May the Force be with you.\"", "\"It's a trap!\"", "\"I've got a bad feeling about this.\"", "\"Do or do not. There is no try.\""]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q10 - Which planet would you most like to visit?",
      "answers": ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Dagobah", "Endor", "Bespin"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q11 - Who is the most underrated character?",
      "answers": ["Chewbacca", "Lando Calrissian", "Mon Mothma", "Wedge Antilles", "R2-D2"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q12 - What was the most emotional scene?",
      "answers": ["Han being frozen in carbonite", "Vader's redemption", "Yoda’s death", "Luke confronting Vader", "Leia's message to Obi-Wan"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q13 - Which droid is your favorite?",
      "answers": ["R2-D2", "C-3PO", "IG-88", "Mouse Droid"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q14 - What is the best Star Wars quote for motivation?",
      "answers": ["\"Do or do not. There is no try.\"", "\"The Force will be with you, always.\"", "\"Never tell me the odds!\"", "\"Strike me down, and I will become more powerful than you can possibly imagine.\""]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q15 - Which faction would you join?",
      "answers": ["Rebellion", "Empire", "Bounty Hunters", "Jedi Order"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q16 - Who is the most powerful Force user?",
      "answers": ["Luke Skywalker", "Darth Vader", "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "Yoda", "Emperor Palpatine"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q17 - What is the best space battle in the original trilogy?",
      "answers": ["Battle of Yavin (Death Star)", "Battle of Hoth", "Battle of Endor"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q18 - Who had the best costume design?",
      "answers": ["Princess Leia", "Darth Vader", "Boba Fett", "Han Solo", "Luke Skywalker"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q19 - Which lightsaber color would you choose?",
      "answers": ["Blue", "Green", "Red", "Yellow"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q20 - What was the funniest scene in the original trilogy?",
      "answers": ["Han and Leia’s banter", "Chewbacca’s game with the droids", "Yoda testing Luke on Dagobah", "Han’s bluff on the Death Star intercom"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q21 - Which villain was the most memorable?",
      "answers": ["Darth Vader", "Emperor Palpatine", "Boba Fett", "Grand Moff Tarkin", "Jabba the Hutt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q22 - What would you do if you had the Force?",
      "answers": ["Train as a Jedi", "Become a bounty hunter", "Fight for the Rebellion", "Explore the galaxy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q23 - Which musical score stands out the most?",
      "answers": ["Main Theme", "Imperial March", "Binary Sunset", "Cantina Band", "Duel of the Fates"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q24 - What is your opinion on the Ewoks?",
      "answers": ["Adorable", "Annoying", "Heroic", "Overrated"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Q25 - Which training scene is the best?",
      "answers": ["Luke on Dagobah", "Obi-Wan’s guidance on the Death Star", "Yoda lifting the X-wing", "Lightsaber practice with remote"]
    }
  ]
}
